promojukebox.com 2016-05-09

# PromoJukeBox - watermarked music promotion

## DATA PROTECTION DISCLOSURE  
of Push Media Promotion GmbH

### 1\. General

| 1.1.| We will process your personal information (e.g., title, name, address, email address, telephone number) only in accordance with the provisions of the German data protection laws. The following rules are intended to inform you about the nature, scope and purpose of collecting, processing and using personal data. This data protection disclosure relates solely to our websites.  
---|---  
  
### 2\. Automatic data logging

2.1.| For technical reasons, we log, among other things, the following data which your Internet browser transmits to us:  
---|---  
  
  * Browser type and browser version

  * Operating system used

  * Website, from which you have visit our website (referrer URL)

  * Websites, which you have visit

  * Date and time of your access

  * Your Internet protocol (IP) address.

2.2.| This anonymous data is stored separately from the personal data which you may have provided us and will thereby not allow any tracing back to a specific person. This data will be analysed for statistical purposes only, in order to optimise our web presentation and the services we offer. The data will be destroyed after it is analysed.  
  
### 3\. Inventory data

3.1.| Your personal data will be used solely for implementing the contract, to the extent the data is needed to establish, draft or modify the contract (inventory data). Your personal data will not be disclosed to any third parties who are not directly involved in the contract implementation, unless you have provided your express consent or the disclosure is allowed by law.  
---|---  
3.2.| If ordered by the competent agencies, we may in some cases disclose inventory data, where it is necessary for purposes of criminal prosecution, for the police to protect against dangers, for meeting the statutory responsibilities of the Federal or State government agencies charged with protecting the Constitution, the Federal Intelligence Agency (Bundesnachrichtendienstes) or the Military Counter-Intelligence Service (Militärischen Abschirmdienstes), or for purposes of enforcing intellectual property rights.  
  
### 4\. Usage data

4.1.| Your personal data, which is required in order to facilitate and invoice the use of our services (usage data), will be utilised for contract implementation purposes. Usage data includes, above all, features to identify you, information concerning the beginning, conclusion and scope of any relevant usage, and information about the teleservices which you have used. We may disclose to other providers or third parties usage data for billing purposes (so-called "billing information"), if this disclosure is required in order to bill the user. Such usage and billing information will be deleted when it is no longer needed to perform or implement the contract. If a deletion would violate certain mandatory retention periods required by law, articles of association or contract, then the data or information will instead be blocked.  
---|---  
4.2.| If ordered by the competent agencies, we may in some cases disclose usage data, where it is necessary for purposes of criminal prosecution, for the police to protect against dangers, for meeting the statutory responsibilities of the Federal or State government agencies charged with protecting the Constitution, the Federal Intelligence Agency (Bundesnachrichtendienstes) or the Military Counter-Intelligence Service (Militärischen Abschirmdienstes), or for purposes of enforcing intellectual property rights.  
  
### 5\. Information regarding cookies

5.1.| If you use our website, certain information may be collected from your computer in the course of your use of our website. We may use both session based and persistent "cookies" and/or other technology (e.g., web bugs, e-mail bugs, clear GIFs, web beacons, tracker GIFs and "clickstream" data logs) in our website or in our electronic communications with you to enhance the functionality of our website and services. These technologies also make your transactions and other activities more convenient and efficient. "Cookies" are small text files, which are filed and saved in the Internet browser on your computer. When you re-download our page, these cookies transmit information which allows us to automatically recognise you. The information retrieved in this manner serves to optimise our services and allow you to access our websites more easily. It is our policy not to save sensitive data, such as passwords or credit card information in cookies.  
---|---  
5.2.| Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can block cookies from being saved on your hard disc by simply selecting "do no accept cookies" in your browser settings. Such a setting could, however, limit the functionality of our website. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to log in into your account or set personalized preferences for your re-visit.  
5.3.| We have two primary uses for cookies. First, we use them to specify a user's preferences. For example, we use cookies to store information about your language preferences so you don't have to choose repeatedly your language. Second, we use cookies to track website usage trends and patterns. This helps us understand our users' needs better and improve areas of our website. We will also use the information to tailor our marketing efforts to be specific to what we believe you will find interesting and relevant.  
  
### 6\. Information

6.1.| Upon request, you may contact Push Media Promotion GmbH, Dorfstr. 12b, 85591 Vaterstetten by telephone at +49 (0) 89 457 087 42 in order to obtain information regarding data about you or your pseudonym. You may also email your questions to us at [info@promojukebox.com](mailto:info@promojukebox.com)  
---|---  
  
_Push Media Promotion GmbH, Stand April 2014_
